So don't stop chasing it until you smile
Little singing bird
MashuLulu-san, you exploded in popularity
right after you made your debut, yes?
Thank you.
Would you say this greatly changed your life?
Yes.
I'm so happy to have made my debut
and to be singing so many lovely songs.
I never imagined I could ever be in this position.
I see!
I feel as though I'm slowly becoming
someone else...
a version of me that's different, and new.
Lulu's so lovely!
That's great to hear!
Yeah.
I look forward to seeing your future work.
Lilly's supposed to show up too after this.
I can't wait!
Thank you!
Thank you very much.
Great work today.
You too.
Oh, Lulu-chan!
Lilly-san!
What's up? You have a gig?
Yes! We just finished filming!
What about you?
I'm on my way to the briefing for Rowdy Talk!
Good luck!
Yeah.
Thanks! See you later, Lulu-chan!
See you later!
I'll come pick you up when you're done.
Okay! Thank you!
I'm home.
Bae, bae, bae, bae, bae, bae, bae, bae, bae
Bae, bae, bae
Bubee, bubee
Bae, bae, bae, bae, bae, bae, bae, bae, bae
Ooh, ooh, ooh
You're my little buddy
Magical Sisters LuluttoLilly
Hey, bubee love
Bubee, bubee, bubee love
Magical Sisters LuluttoLilly
My heart is racing like crazy
And right before my eyes
Are the colors of a brand new world
Whoa
Stay with me today
We'll walk hand in hand
Dreaming of the place where we can become light
I can hear the magic
I wanna sing with you
Let's sing together
You're a bright shining star
My bubee, bubee, bubee love
We can be shining stars
Forever and ever
That's our secret magic
My bubee, bubee, bubee love
Ooh, ooh, ooh
You're my little buddy
Hey, bubee love
Bubee, bubee, bubee love
Bae, bae, bae, bae, bae, bae, bae, bae, bae
Bae, bae, bae
Bubee, bubee
B-U-B-E-E, bubee
Bubee love
An Unsatisfying Saturday
Strawberry daifuku
Cuts open
Apple
Leaf only
Flower only
G'morning...
Where's big sis?
Rui went out earlier.
She's been out a lot lately.
Huh, really?
Did something good happen to her?
Bye, Mom!
Take care!
Another gig?
It's a meeting for a new show!
Since I'm super popular.
Lililula, palilula! Pam pam power!
Morning!
Lulu-chan!
Huh? Is it just you?
Good morning.
Toko-san asked me to stay here.
Operations Schedule
Name
Plan
Remarks
President
Toko
Sena
Lilly
around 1pm
Off
Away
Really?
Wanna wait for her together?
Three sugar cubes, right?
Y-Yes. Thank you...
Hey, why so stiff?
You can be casual with me.
U-Um, it's just...
You're a big inspiration to me, Lilly-san.
I am?
Y-You're very cute,
and everything you do is fun!
Just looking at you makes me feel happy!
I-I'm sorry!
You mentioned before
that I inspired you, right?
I'm flattered, but why me?
When I saw you singing...
it made me feel deep down
that I wanted to sing like that too.
Huh? Nah...
You're way cooler than me!
Not at all! Don't say that...
I enjoy being an idol,
but I dunno what I want to do after this.
Ever since I was little,
there's this girl I really loved.
I really wanted to see her smile,
and it ended up turning into a whole thing.
I'm not totally sure myself
if I'm doing the right thing or not.
I think you should keep doing this.
You're making people smile!
If I had never met you,
things probably would have never changed.
You opened the door for me, Lilly-san.
I see! Then I'll keep going for you, Lulu-chan!
Ugh, oh boy. I feel so awkward.
M-Me too, but thank you.
Hello?
Sorry to ruin the mood here...
T-T-Toko-san!
How long have you...?!
I got here a bit ago,
but you never noticed.
Now I feel awkward too...
Lulu, thanks for watching the place.
N-No problem.
Here. It's the script for your next program.
You can head home for the day.
O-Okay. Thank you very much.
You're about to get a lot busier, you two!
Alright! Let's get to work!
This is no time for flirting, you know!
We were not!
I'm home.
You've been busy. Are you resting well?
I'm home...
Oh, plenty!
I can rest just about anywhere!
Huh? It's me!
Do you doze off in dressing rooms?
Big sis never watches TV...
Sometimes!
You're even sleeping now.
What?!
Gotcha! I'm just kidding.
You scared me.
Did you nap in the dressing room today?
Oh, not today. I had this really yummy bento lunch!
Big sis!
Welcome home, Fuu.
Big sis, are you a fan of Lilly?
Just wondering, since you never watch stuff like this.
Yes, I like her.
I didn't know!
Lilly's super popular at school!
Isn't she so cool?
No.
What?!
"Cool" doesn't describe her.
She's really amazing!
Really?
Yeah.
She has gained a lot of fans lately.
And she's been getting a lot more TV work.
I didn't think you'd know about her!
So, what do you like about Lilly, big sis?
Her singing.
Huh? Really?
Please, it's not all that.
I take off my sneakers, feeling I've grown
Bout to head out in my new fit
Earrings dangling, lip gloss on
I want to hear you sing again.
Somehow dazzling even inside
It all seemed like a fairy tale on a screen
I can't.
Why not? Your singing was so lovely.
Something far, far away I could never reach
But I leap onto the crossing, perhaps I'll find my love
No it wasn't. I just...
And cast a spell on you
I mean it! You were such a good singer!
Sing with me
Su-Sugar Sugarly La Lu Sugarin'
Better than Lilly, even!
I should know, I listened to you sing so much!
I'll coat even your sighs in sugar
Even the same old bustling intersection
This is the truth!
Can become a stage with a touch of magic
Su-Sugar Sugarly La Lu Sugarin'
Big sis...
Please sing.
Every lost gaze, come to me
It's not that simple.
I'll stuff a balloon full of sparkly lights
And create a wonderland
Lilly...-chan...
is far better than me,
but that doesn't matter.
I can't sing like that.
I'm out in search of thrills
That I can't predict, that I've never seen before
That's not true! I mean it, big sis!
Anywhere is my runway, and I can't stop
Because I know all about Lilly!
And I'll take it on as my best self
When our eyes meet, a shooting star bursts past
You don't know anything, Fuu.
About me or Lilly-chan.
I hope my heartstrings start to twinkle
I do know! Because I'm...
I want to see you, honey, is now a bad time?
I'll make it happen with magic
I'm going upstairs.
Are you okay?
I've never seen you upset...
I don't get it either.
I didn't mean to say that...
Rui...
Lilly-chan said she wanted
to make everyone smile.
I could never compare to that.
I was really mean to Fuu...
I just can't tell her!
I know Lilly better than anyone else!
That's why I said what I said!
I just want big sis...
Oh no.
Dummy!
Let's go.
What's the matter?
Here, have one.
I'm good.
I had a fight with big sis.
Wow, that's rare.
Good for you.
Huh? No it's not!
Sorry. I'm sure you don't feel good.
Did you make up?
Nope, not yet.
Big sis went out somewhere.
I see.
Just wait for now.
I'm sure you'll get to patch things up later.
Go on, take this.
It's our new product for this fall.
I'm going out to play.
Okay. Have fun!
Letto!
Lululila, pululila!
Pop'n pam!
I want to find something sparkly.
Did it work?
Lulu?
Let's go, Azuki.
Okay!
Going to the agency?
Nope, it's my day off.
Looking at lots of cute things will cheer me up!
Aww, cute!
This is cute too!
This looks nice!
Big sis would look good on this.
No, don't!
Ooh, that looks yummy!
Which one should I pick...?
Too many snacks.
Huh?
You just ate a manju earlier, no?
It's okay for today! I'm clearing my mind.
Thank you for coming in!
Big sis, is it good?
Yes, very yummy!
You two get along so well.
Yeah!
Not getting any?
I changed my mind.
I wanted some ice cream...
Got a cavity?
No way.
I just feel so foggy.
This is so unsatisfying!
Lililula, palilula!
Make my fog go away!
Huh? That's it?
Nothing's changed...
I guess you failed.
You be quiet.
Push Button at Night
Let's go home.
Nuh-uh. I'm not having fun yet.
I'm tired...
Uguisu, you aren't even walking.
You've been on my bag all day.
No Entry
What the?
It's a dead end.
Road Closed
Over here too.
See? We can't go back to the train.
Darn.
No Entry
A dead end?
I'll head that way.
I guess I'll cross over there.
Wait!
Lulu-chan?
Wait up!
Lilly-san?!
Let's go, before the light changes!
O-Okay!
Here.
Thank you.
That was a surprise.
I didn't expect to run into you.
Me neither. What brings you out here?
I came out here to clear my mind.
Window shopping, looking at cute clothes.
I needed some fresh air too.
Wow! So we're alike!
So, then I found this ice cream shop.
Did you eat there?
No...
Didn't feel like it.
Did something happen?
Huh?
You're acting different from yesterday.
Like you're in a bad mood.
Imagine you had manju you wanted to eat,
and you set it aside for later,
because you really wanted to have it
with the person you love.
But then you mess up, and don't get to eat it at all.
Is that so?
Yeah. I wanted to eat together
and have a fun chat, but I ruined it.
Manju sure don't last long, do they?
Exactly!
Do you like sweets?
Hmm... Kinda.
Me too.
And I know how you feel.
I've messed up before too.
You have?
Yes.
Like when I can't honestly
speak what's on my mind.
You're always honest, Lulu-chan.
No, I'm not really that honest at all.
Really?
I can be open when I'm with you, but not usually.
So I tend to hate myself.
That happens to me too!
Ever since this morning,
I've felt all foggy, like, "why?"
So we're alike.
Road Closed
The manju problem is solved now, I think.
I really wanted to eat together,
but I couldn't say it,
and then I took my anger out on someone else.
I see it now...
I might've been upset with myself back then.
Don't feel sad, Lulu-chan!
Even if I'm still gloomy myself.
Maybe that's kinda selfish.
I think you're pretty honest, Lilly-san.
Am I?
Yes! And I love that.
If you say so, then I'll think it too!
Good!
Talking with you really cheered me up.
Thanks!
Me too. You made me feel a lot better.
I'll try to be open about how I feel.
Good for them!
Oh, you...
By the way...
you didn't run away from home, did you?
Huh?! I didn't, I swear!
Oh, okay! That's a relief.
'Cause earlier, you just seemed so... y'know.
I swear, it's not like that!
I'm home...
Welcome home.
H-Hi, I'm back.
Fuu.
Huh?
I'm sorry.
I-It's okay!
Courage is in two worlds, yeah, together now
(Proof!)
It's what binds us together
Everyone smiles at the beautiful girls
(My dream!)
I just wanna know what the future holds
(Alone!)
Even if the stars in a moonless sky
Still twinkle
(No magic!)
Even if the clouds in a sunless sky
Still drift
I feel so lonely
(I was always right beside you)
I'm searching for you
I'll frame a photo of us two and hang it up
Let's set things the way we want, the way we will, the way they are
Take our chemistry, plus+, minus-, multiplied×, divided÷ by...
I love it every way
Calling me, calling you
(And you)
I want to walk up the stairs of the future with you
Lucky lucky shiny, our beating hearts dreamin' away
If there's clear skies tomorrow, everything will be okay
Maybe I'm a bit sad and weak
(But I'm happy!)
But when I'm with you I feel safe
There's no such thing as wasted time
Let's wait until the rain stops
Check it out, look up at the sky
Courage is in two worlds, yeah, together now
(Proof!)
That's what binds us together
Everyone smiles at the beautiful girls
What kind of future will the spotlight shine on?
You're Invited to Felix Star